hungertv.com 2018-06-04

# Privacy Policy | HUNGER TV

This notice describes the Hunger Publishing privacy policy, which applies to this website (hungertv.com) and the services provided with this website (for example our newsletters and competitions). By visiting our website you are agreeing and consenting to the practices described in this privacy policy and our _cookie policy_.

If you do not accept this privacy policy you are not authorised to access or otherwise use this website or associated services such as our competitions, newsletters or to submit content for our site and you should cease all use of our services immediately. 

This policy may change from time to time so you should ensure that you check frequently for any updates. All subscribers to our newsletters will be notified when our privacy policy is updated.

## Managing your privacy

When you supply any information to us we have legal obligations towards you regarding the way that we use your information and to use it fairly. It is important to us that you are able to access our services without compromising your privacy unreasonably. Personal information is any information that allows someone to identify you, including for example your name, address, telephone or IP address. 

In general, any information you provide to hungertv.com will only be used by hungertv.com and its partners for delivering services to you and for improving the performance of our services. Whenever you use our website information will be collected through the use of cookies. If you subscribe to our newsletters, provide content for our competitions or contact us for any other means we will retain your information for so long as is reasonably necessary but not unduly or without purpose. 

You can read more about our partners and their access to your information in our _cookie policy_. You should also read our _terms of use_ before using our site and by using this site you agree to be bound by these conditions. If you do not agree to our _terms of use_ you should cease use of our services immediately. 

Please do not submit any personal information to us if you do not want us to store or process it. 

## INFORMATION WE STORE AND PROCESS

Your personal information may be processed both in and outside of the UK. When you submit your details in whichever country you are situated you agree to the information being processed in the UK. 

We may also process or transfer your personal information outside of the UK or the European Economic Area and may permit service providers outside of these territories such as those in the USA to process your information on our behalf. For example we use partners to host our mailing lists and to provide us with analysis of user behaviours or browsing activity that are located are outside of the EU. 

In such instances we use all reasonable efforts to ensure that these partners are committed to the same level of privacy using the EU framework agreement protocol. However whilst we are committed to delivering the same level of privacy through our partnerships we cannot guarantee this. If you do not agree to our partners having access to your information in order to provide our services to you you should cease use of our services immediately.

## Keeping information safe

We use industry standard partners to provide our services however no transmission of data over the internet is 100% guaranteed as risk free. We will use all reasonable measures to ensure your data is secure however access of our services and sharing of your personal information is at your own risk.

## How long will you hold personal information

We will hold personal information only so long as necessary to deliver our services, to retain relevant records for material you have submitted to us or until you opt out of our services, unless otherwise required by a court of law.

## Our partners

Third parties will be granted access to your information (which is in most cases anonymised) in order to deliver our services to you. Our partners may use information to track and report on your browser activity, deliver you targeted advertising and provide a personalised service for your visit to our site based on your activity and interests. Our partners for managing the performance of the site or delivering content that is tailored to your interests are outlined in more detail in our _cookie policy_. 

We use Mailchimp to provide the hosting and fulfilment of our weekly news updates, Linode for hosting of our website and Google Analytics for tracking our user behaviours. Their privacy policies can be found by clicking on their links below:

 _[Mailchimp  
](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/?_ga=2.39315235.1048986590.1527118351-862274827.1527118351)_[Linode  
](https://www.linode.com/privacy)_[Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks?hl=en&gl=de)_

We do not share any personal information with any third parties other than with the partners who provide the services to you and we will use all reasonable measures to limit distribution of your personal information unless required by a court of law.

## Contacting us

If you would like any further information or want to contact us regarding your personal information you can write to us at: 

The Data Controller  
Hunger Publishing Limited  
110-114 Grafton Road  
London NW5 4BA.
